const Game2Data = [
  {
    _id: "672f046eb99db74d3a467c3c",
    questionText: "What is JSX?",
    options: [
      "A syntax extension for JavaScript",
      "A templating engine",
      "A JavaScript framework",
      "A JavaScript library",
    ],
    scores: [80, 20, 0, 0],
    correctOptions: [0, 1],
    level: "671b261da20924624e9cf00d",
    answer: null,
    score: 0,
  },
  {
    _id: "672f046eb99db74d3a467c45",
    questionText:
      "Which of the following hooks are used for side effects in React?",
    options: ["useEffect", "useLayoutEffect", "useState", "useCallback"],
    scores: [60, 40, 0, 0],
    correctOptions: [0, 1],
    level: "671b261da20924624e9cf00d",
    answer: null,
    score: 0,
  },
  {
    _id: "672f046eb99db74d3a467c3d",
    questionText: "What does the 'useEffect' hook do in React?",
    options: [
      "Runs side effects",
      "Handles form submissions",
      "Manages state",
      "Triggers re-renders",
    ],
    scores: [80, 0, 0, 50],
    correctOptions: [0, 3],
    level: "671b261da20924624e9cf00d",
    answer: null,
    score: 0,
  },
  {
    _id: "672f046eb99db74d3a467c3f",
    questionText: "What is the purpose of the 'key' prop in React lists?",
    options: [
      "To uniquely identify elements",
      "To define the order of elements",
      "To store the element's data",
      "To trigger a re-render of the list",
    ],
    scores: [100, 0, 0, 0],
    correctOptions: [0],
    level: "671b261da20924624e9cf00d",
    answer: null,
    score: 0,
  },
  {
    _id: "672f046eb99db74d3a467c3b",
    questionText: "Which of the following is a lifecycle method in React?",
    options: [
      "componentDidMount",
      "componentWillUnmount",
      "shouldComponentUpdate",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    scores: [30, 30, 40, 0],
    correctOptions: [0, 1, 2],
    level: "671b261da20924624e9cf00d",
    answer: null,
    score: 0,
  },
  {
    _id: "672f046eb99db74d3a467c41",
    questionText: "What is the 'context' API used for in React?",
    options: [
      "Passing data through the component tree without manually passing props",
      "Managing state locally within a component",
      "Optimizing performance",
      "Handling routing",
    ],
    scores: [100, 0, 0, 0],
    correctOptions: [0],
    level: "671b261da20924624e9cf00d",
    answer: null,
    score: 0,
  },
  {
    _id: "672f046eb99db74d3a467c42",
    questionText: "Which of the following are valid hooks in React?",
    options: ["useState", "useEffect", "useReducer", "useDirective"],
    scores: [40, 40, 20, 0],
    correctOptions: [0, 1, 2],
    level: "671b261da20924624e9cf00d",
    answer: null,
    score: 0,
  },
  {
    _id: "672f046eb99db74d3a467c3a",
    questionText:
      "Which of the following are valid state management methods in React?",
    options: ["useState", "setState", "useEffect", "redux"],
    scores: [40, 40, 0, 100],
    correctOptions: [0, 1, 3],
    level: "671b261da20924624e9cf00d",
    answer: null,
    score: 0,
  },
  {
    _id: "672f046eb99db74d3a467c44",
    questionText: "Which of the following are correct for React context?",
    options: [
      "Context provides a way to pass data through the component tree",
      "Context can replace Redux for state management",
      "Context is only used for theming",
      "Context is not reactive",
    ],
    scores: [80, 20, 0, 0],
    correctOptions: [0, 1],
    level: "671b261da20924624e9cf00d",
    answer: null,
    score: 0,
  },
  {
    _id: "672f046eb99db74d3a467c3e",
    questionText:
      "Which of the following are valid ways to pass data to a React component?",
    options: ["Props", "State", "Context", "Ref"],
    scores: [50, 30, 20, 0],
    correctOptions: [0, 1, 2],
    level: "671b261da20924624e9cf00d",
    answer: null,
    score: 0,
  },
];

export default Game2Data;
